Contact

aaqilcr6@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aakil-zihaf-398281231 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Fusion Splicing SQL JavaScript

Aakil Zihaf

Student at Wayamba University of Sri Lanka

Colombo, Western Province, Sri Lanka

Summary

I am Aakil Zihaf (982022975V) from Kalmunai. I was born on 1998.07.20 and now I am 24 years old. I was completed my GCE (O/L) and GCE (A/L). I was completed Information Communication Technology Technician (NVQ Level 04) in Sammanthurai Technical College and Diploma in ICT (NVQ Level 05) in College of Technology Maradana. Now I am following Higher Diploma in Software Engineering in Wayamba University of Sri Lanka. I have one year intern experience at National Water supply and Drainage Board and Sri Lanka Telecom PLC.

Experience

Sri Lanka Telecom Network Specialist March 2022 - September 2022 (7 months) Kalmunai, Eastern Province, Sri Lanka

####Key responsibilities####

- 1. Fiber Spicing
- 2.4G, ADSL and Fiber Router Configuration
- 3. Provide IP TV Connection Via 4G, Fiber and Copper
- 4. Maintain Remote switching Unit

National Water Supply and Drainage Board Information Communication Technology Technician August 2019 - February 2022 (2 years 7 months)

Kalmunai, Eastern Province, Sri Lanka

####Key responsibilities####

- 1.Consumer details update and get their information in Water Board online Commercial System.
- 2.Using Internet and E-Mail for sent an office document. Reset and Re-Installing windows for office computers.
- 3. Assisting to IT in-charge to troubleshoot wireless network

and system issue.

4.Used Google Map and google Earth for measuring area and Pipe line.

Education

Wayamba University of Sri Lanka

Diploma of Education, Computer Software Engineering · (March 2021 - March 2022)

Maradana College of Technology

Diploma, Information Technology · (2020 - 2022)

Wayamba University of Sri Lanka

Higher National Diploma, Computer Software Engineering · (March 2022)